[Music]
poof I got my buddy Seth Rogen come on I
I adore this guy I adore this guy
he's a great writer a great friend and
we can't talk about Seth without talking
about the Green Hornet we just can't
right because every person in the world
is like The Green Hornet lost so much
money but that's not true it didn't lose
that much money I mean every single
person in the world hated it but
it didn't lose that much money and
that's the goal after all right to make
terrible movies that don't lose that
much money that's awesome now
James the main course the feast de
resistance
James loves education he's always going
to school did you know that he even went
to Yale okay look I know what you're
thinking and it's not true he got into
Yale just like everybody else he got
really really famous and just kind of
asked a person from Yale if he could go
there just like everybody else
and everyone is gonna make fun of James
for the Oscars it's obvious everyone was
saying James was dead up there but I
think that was Anne Hathaway's fault I
mean her for trying like at all how
dare she attempt in some way to
entertain the millions of people trying
to escape their lives for a few hours I
commend you James you know you always
hear George Clooney and other big movie
stars saying my philosophy on making
movies is one for them and one for me
but not my guy James James is a rebel he
has his own philosophy on this one for
them five for nobody
[Applause]
[Music]